Finding Aid for the Horace Tapscott Papers PASC-M.0237
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound Recordings, Series 1.
  - Assorted Identified Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Personnel includes: Al Hines; Roberto Miguel Miranda; Daaood Woods; Billy Hinton, drums; Sabir Mateen, tenor saxophone; Jon Williams, baritone saxophone and bass clarinet; Aubrey Hart, fl & piccolo; Adele Sebastian, fl and vocal; Billie Harris, soprano saxophone; Lester Robertson, trombone; Horatio Tapscott. Note: Bidlack and Albach recording. Part 1 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Personnel: Al Hines; Roberto Miranda; Daaood Woods; Billy Hinton, drums; Sabir Mateen, tenor; Jon Williams, baritone saxophone and bass clarinet; Aubrey Hart, flute & piccolo; Adele, flute and vocal; Billie Harris, soprano saxophone; Lester Robertson; Horatio Tapscott. Note: Bidlack and Albach recording. Part 2 of 2.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      2 tapes: part 1.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 June 24 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      part 2 of 2
    - PAPA Live at the century City Playhouse, 09/09/1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), live at Century City Playhouse, 1979 September 9; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 37)
      (rehearsal: Nation Rising?)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 September 30 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 September 30 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 September 30; Tape 3 of 4. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 September 30; Tape 4 of 4. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - No location, 1979 October 27 - 1979 November 4; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 76, Folder 38)
      Compositions: Horacio -- Lullaby for Linda -- Jitterbug Waltz -- Daydreaming -- In Times Like These.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC, 1979 November 25 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Horatio, Nation Rising (Samahi- sp) -- Faith / Roberto MM -- Carnival.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, David Bryant, Linda, p and voc, Dadisi Wells, tenor, Sabir Mateen, tenor, Adele Sebastian, flute and vocal; Billy Hinton, drums, Roberto Miguel Miranda, Juana Nash, trumpet, Al Hines, Jujigwa (Juan Gray), vocal, Louis Spears, cello, Virgil Figueroa, congas, Mitchico Sanchez, timbales.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC - Last Sunday of the Month Concert, 1979 November 25; 1 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Compositions: Horacio -- Nation Rising.
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott, piano; David B; Linda, piano and vocals; Dadisi Wells, tenor sax; Sabir Mateen, tenor sax; Adele, flute and vocal; Billy Hinton, drums; Roberto MM, bass; Juana Nash, trumpet; Al Hines; Jujigwa (Juan Gray), vocal; Louis Spears, cello; Virgil Figueroa, congas; Mitchito Sanchez, timbales.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC - Last Sunday of the Month Concert, 1979 November 25; 2 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Nation Rising -- Faith.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; David B; Linda, piano and vocals; Dadisi Wells, tenor sax; Sabir M, tenor sax; Adele, flute and vocal; Billy Hinton, drums; Roberto MM; Juana Nash, trumpet; Al Hines; Jujigwa (Juan Gray), vocal; Louis Spears, cello; Virgil Figueroa, congas; Mitchito Sanchez, timbales.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at the IUCC - Last Sunday of the Month Concert, 1979 November 25 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Carnival.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; David B; Linda, piano and vocals; Dadisi Wells, tenor sax; Sabir M, tenor sax; Adele, flute and vocal; Billy Hinton, drums; Roberto MM; Juana Nash, trumpet; Al Hines; Jujigwa (Juan Gray), vocal; Louis Spears, cello; Virgil Figueroa, congas; Mitchito Sanchez, timbales. Tape 3 of performance recorded on 3 tapes.
    - Horacio, 11/25/1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      PAPA at the IUCC
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; David B; Linda, piano and vocal; Dadisi Wells, tenor; Sabir M, tenor; Adele, flute and vocal; Billy Hinton, drums; Roberto MM; Juana Nash, trumpet; Al Hines; Jujigwa (Juan Gray), vocal; Louis Spears, cello; Virgil Figueroa, congas; Mitchito Sanchez, timbales
      Compositions: Horacio, Nation Rising (Samahi), Faith (Roberto MM), Carnival
    - The Call, 12/22/1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Compositions: The Call, In Times Like These
    - Lino's Tune, 12/1979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Compositions: Lino's Tune, Drunken Mary
    - People Like Us/World Peace, 01/12/1980; 1 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Personnel: Fundi; Adele; Kafi; Herbert Calles; David B; Al Hines; Linda; Billy Hinton; JuJigwa; Horace Tapscott
      Compositions: People Like Us, World Peace
    - People Like Us/World Peace, 01/12/1980; 2 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Ark Rehearsal, 1980 January 19 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Personnel: David B; Kafi, flute; JuJigwa, vocal; Sabir Mateen, tenor; Billy Hinton, drum; Dadisi Wells, tenor; Adele Sebastian, flute; Horace Tapscott.
    - World Peace, 01/24/1980 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      Ark Rehearsal
      Compositions: World Peace, People Like Us
    - World Peace, 01/26/1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - UGMAA Shop, 02/07/1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Byron Pope, alto sax; Sabir, tenor sax; Billy Hinton, drums; David B; Al Hines
    - Century City Playhouse, 1980 February 10; 3 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Horace Tapscott Trio: Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Al Hines; Byron Pope; David B; Billy Hinton; Sabir.
    - The ARK at the IUCC, 02/24/1980; 1 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      No Info. - Possibly Last Sunday Concert, Nimbus Recordings
    - The ARK at the IUCC, 02/24/1980; 2 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - The ARK at the IUCC, 02/24/1980; 4 of 5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - The Ark at the IUCC, 02/24/1980; 3 of 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - The Ark at the IUCC, 02/24/1980; 5 of 5 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - [Selections], 1980 March 22 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Compositions: Dream Nigga -- Nothing -- I Felt Spring -- Fo Fats.
    - Fo Fats, 03/22/1980 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Nothing(?), I Felt Spring, Fo Fats, Dream Nigga (Linda Hill)
    - No location, 03/22/1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Compositions: Nothing (?), I felt Spring, Fo Fats, Dream Nigga (Linda Hill)
    - Nothing, 03/22/1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Compositions: Nothing, I Felt Spring, Fo Fats, Dream Nigga (Linda Hill)
    - Tapscott at Church, 03/30/1980; 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Possibly IUCC, Nimbus Recordings
    - Tapscott at Church, 03/30/1980; 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Prayer #1, 04/12/1980; 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Personnel: Everett Brown; Horace Tapscott; David B; Al Hines; Ishmael Balaka; Kafi; Sabir; Kufahamu; Fundi; Adele
      Compositions: Prayer #1 (Roberto Miranda), Nothing, Reincarnation of a Lovebird (Mingus)
    - Prayer #1, 04/12/1980; 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Rehearsal Tapes, 04/14/1980 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Personnel: Everett; Horace Tapscott; David B; Michael Dett and Jihad, engineers
      Compositions: 6/8 D minor Blues Thing (Horace Tapscott - probably improvised), Dance Children, Leland's Song (Linda Hill)
    - Rehearsal Tapes, 04/14/1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      Compositions: 6/8 D minor blues thing (HT probably improvised), Dance Children, Leland's Song (Linda Hill)
    - The ARK at the IUCC, 04/27/1980; 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Possibly Nimbus Recordings
    - The ARK at IUCC, 04/27/1980; 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - B of C Concert, 1980 May 10 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Compositions: Linda Hill trilogy: The Dou, Sammalli Man, Barneo, Bush Nigga.
      Personnel: Linda Hill; Al Hines; David B. Fundi, trumpet; Sabir Mateen, tenor sax; JuJigwa (Juan Gray), vocal.
    - UGMAA Foundation Jazz cat. IV, 07/13/1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Nation Rising, 10/11/1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      Compositions: Nation Rising (Semahi Hakim)
    - No location, 1981; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 72)
      1. Leland's song: Linda Hill
      2. Creator's Musicians: Linda Hill
      3. Lullaby for Linda: Linda Hill
      4. Children: Linda Hill
      1. One step out: B.J.& Bob Crowley Jr.
      2. Stars in light year time: B.J.& Bob Crowley Jr.
      3. Flashback in time: B.J.& Bob Crowley Jr.
      4. All praise is due: B.J.& Bob Crowley Jr.
    - IUCC, 1981 February 22 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Personnel: Dadisi Wells, tenor; Bob Crowley, piano; Greg Adams, drums; John, trumpet; Kamonta Polk, bass; Linda Hill, vocals; Adele, vocals; JuJigwa, vocals.
    - IUCC, 1981 February 22 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Dadisi Wells, tenor; Bob Crowley, piano; Greg Adams, drums; John, trumpet; Kamonta Polk, bass; Linda Hill, vocal; Adele, vocal; JuJigwa, vocal
      Compositions: So what, Moments Notice, Equinox, Milestones, Priestess
    - Checking In (theme), 1981 April 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Compositions: Checking In theme (theme for TV series that dealt with Marla Gibbs).
    - IUCC, 1981 April 26 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      The Arkestra. Compositions: Les, Mary on Sunday, Motherless Child, King's Chamber (another group)
      Compositions: Rise Together with the Dawn, Natty Dread
    - The ARK at The IUCC, 04/26/1981 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Les, Mary on Sunday, Motherless Child, King's Chamber (Another group)
      Compositions: Rise Together with the Dawn, Natty Dread.
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 May 17 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Personnel: Aubrey Hart, Sabir, David B.
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 May 19 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      On item, "1 of 2."
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 May 19; 7" open reel audio tapes (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - IUCC: Bob Crowley, 1981 May 28; open reel audio tape (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 May 30 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Arkestra at the Shop, 05/31/1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - The Arkestra at the shop, 05/31/1981 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Eaton House Concert, 06/21/1981 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      personnel: Horace Tapscott, Al Hines, henry Frnaklin, fritz wise, Dadisi Wells,
      Compositions: Mary on Sunday, One for Benny.
    - Eaton House concert, 06/21/1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      The Quintet. personnel: Horace Tapscott, AL Hines, Henry Franklin, Fritz, wise, Dadisi wells,
      Compositions: Mary on Sunday, One for Benny. Part 2
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 June 24 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      On item, "Part 1."
    - The ARK at the IUCC, 06/28/1981 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      Part 2
    - Possible blank reel, 06/27/1981? (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - The Ark at the IUCC, 06/28/1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Watts Tower, 07/25/1981; 1 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Watts Tower, 07/25/1981; 2 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      The Ark
    - The Arkestra at the IUCC, 07/26/1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Compositions: For Reverned Edwards, Jungle Juice (Horace Silver), Soulful Days (Cal Massey), Come Sunday (Duke Ellington) As a Child (Horace Tapsoot), Lately's Solo, Black Anthem.
    - Paramount Piano Demo for Tom Albach, 07/26/1981; 1 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Paramount Piano Demo for Tom Albach, 07/26/1981; 2 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Arkestra at the IUCC, 1981 August 30 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Compositions: (A Coltrane Piece) -- Blues for IUCC / The Ark -- Thought of Dar es Salaam.
      "The Last of an Era of Nine Years." Personnel: Adele Sebastian, flute, soprano saxophone; Fuasi, baritone saxophone; Norman Love, tenor saxophone, Charles Chandler, tenor saxophone, Ismael Balaka, Bill Madison, Billy Hinton, drums; Linda Hill, piano & vocals, David Bryant, fundi, french horn; Al Hines, Rick West, bass; Phillip Meeks, trombone; Steve Smith, trumpet; Irwing, alto saxophone & flute; Moses Obligacions, congas; Horace Tapscott, piano and conductor; Michael Dett and Jihad Galloway, engineers; Somaya "Peaches" Hassan, vocals, JuJigwa (Juan Grey), vocals.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Arkestra at the IUCC - "The Last of an Era of Nine Years" (last performance at IUCC, 1981 August 30 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Compositions: (a Coltrane piece) -- Blues for IUCC / the ARK -- Thought of Dar es-Salaam.
      Personnel: Adele Sebastian, flute; Kafi, soprano sax and flute; Fuasi, baritone sax; Norman Love, tenor sax; Charles Chandler, tenor sax; Ismael Balaka, Bill Madison, Billy Hinton, drums; Linda Hill, percussion and vocal; David Bryant; Fundi, french horn; Al Hines; Rick West, bass; Phillip Meeks, trombone; Steve Smith, trumpet; Irwing, alto sax and flute; Moses Obligacion, congas; Horace Tapscott, piano and conductor; Michael Dett and Jihad Galloway, engineers; Somaya "Peaches" Hassan, vocals; JuJigwa (Juan Grey), vocals.
    - ARK at I.U.C.C., 1981 August 30; 7" open reel audio tapes (Box 76, Folder 40)
      On container: Part 1.
    - Creative Arts Ensemble, 10/18/1981; 1 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Sunday, 8:30 pm
    - Creative Arts Ensemble, 10/18/1981; 2 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      KPFK Interview - Reggie Andrews, Ndugu, Kufahamu, Gary Alexander, Horace Tapscott (Kafahamu working at station then - probably did interview)
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 December 25 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 December 25 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      part 3
    - [Contents Unidentified], 1981 December 25; 7" open reel audio tape (Box 72)
      On item: C.S. # 122581, Part 1.
    - Memory Lane, 12/26/1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Memory Lane, 12/26/1981 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      Part 3
    - Memory Lane, 12/26/1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Memory Lane, 08/28/1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Horace Tapscott Quintet plus One
  - Unidentified Sound Recordings, Subseries 2.
    - UGMAA/UCLA, No. B-1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      UN-ID 7" reel to reel tape
    - UGMAA/UCLA, No. B-2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - UGMAA/UCLA, No. B-4 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - UGMAA/UCLA, No. B-5 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-6 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-7 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-8 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-9 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-10 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-11 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-12 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - UGMAA/UCLA, No. B-14 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - UGMAA/UCLA, No. B-15 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - UGMAA/PAPA, No. B-16 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - UGMAA, No. B-17 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - UGMAA, No. B-18 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - UGMAA, No. B-19 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - UGMAA, No. B-20 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - UGMAA, No. B-21 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - UGMAA, No. B-22 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - UGMAA, No. B-23 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - UGMAA, No. B-24 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - UGMAA, No. B-25 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - UGMAA, No. B-26 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - UGMAA, No. B-27 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - UGMAA, No. B-28 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - UGMAA, No. B-29 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - UGMAA, No. B-30 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - UGMAA, No. B-31 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      UN-ID 4" reel to reel tape
    - UGMAA, No. B-32 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - UGMAA, No. B-33 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - UGMAA, No. B-34 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - UGMAA, No. B-35 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - UGMAA, No. B-36 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - UGMAA, No. B-38 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - UGMAA, No. B-38 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - UGMAA, No. B-39 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      (3)UN-ID 7" reel to reel tapes
- Music Manuscripts, Series 2.
  Arrangement note
  The series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Aaron's for Burton (Box 40)
    Ensemble parts for Alto, Tenor, Piano, and Bass.
  - Adell: The Arkette (Orchid) Flower, 3 pages; score (Box 62)
  - Afro Hip, 1 pages (Box 50)
    Saxophone part.
  - Aim (Box 40)
    Lead sheets and ensemble parts for Trumpet, Alto, and Tenor.
  - Ain't Funny (Box 40)
    Parts for Trumpet, Tenor, Bari, and Rhythm.
  - Akirfa, 3p. (Box 62)
    3 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Aminifu: 1. Tao, 2. Somali Man, 3. Borneo Bush Nigguh (Box 40)
    Tenor part only.
  - Ancestral Echoes, Original score and photocopy of score 128p. (2 folders) (Box 50)
    Note on back of original score states that work was first performed at the Music Center in Los Angeles, October 25, 1975.
  - Angel Eyes (Box 40)
    Score and parts for Trombone and Bass.
  - Aries, 11 pages (Box 62)
    8 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Art's Boogie, 2p. (Box 50)
    Lead sheet.
  - Arthur's Vamp, 5 p. (Box 62)
  - As A Child (Box 40)
    Bass part and page two of score
  - As Above, So Below, 44p. (Box 50)
    Music score for the motion picture by the same name, directed by Larry Clark. Score and 18 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - At The Crossroads, 35p. (Box 50)
    Score and 11 ensemble parts for various instruments. Score contains music for Dial "B" For Barbra, and Uhuruh Everybody.
  - Attica, 1 p. (Box 62)
    Piano part.
  - Auction Block, 1 p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheet with lyrics.
  - Azar, 15p. (Box 50)
    13 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Back Beat, 7p. (Box 51)
    Score.
  - Bakai, 3p. (Box 51)
    2 ensemble parts.
  - Ballad For Deadwood Dick, 6p. (Box 51)
  - Ballad For Americans, 16p. (Box 62)
  - Ballad For Samuel, 8p. (Box 51)
    Score and ensemble parts for alto and soprano saxophone.
    Music also included for Daughter of Cochise.
  - Band Flare Opening, 2 p. (Box 40)
    Alto and Tenor parts only.
  - Bavarian Suite (Bavarian Mist), 7p. (Box 51)
    Score and parts for bass and drums.
    Some sheets are titled Bavarian Mist rather than Bavarian Suite.
  - Bee Vamp, 11p. (Box 51)
    Score and 10 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Bird Song (Box 38)
    Ensemble parts for flute, tuba, and bass.
  - Bird Song (Box 51)
    Score and ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - The Black Apostles, 38p. (Box 51)
    Score and 9 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Black Arthur, 32p. (Box 51)
    Score and 16 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - The Black Ballet, 12p. (Box 51)
    11 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Black, Brown, and Yellow, 15p. (Box 51)
    15 ensemble parts for various instruments.
    Composer also known as Guido Sinclair.
  - Black Narcissus, 11p. (Box 51)
  - Blackness, 11p.
    6 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Black World, 34p.
    9 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - The Blessed One, 22p.
    Score and 11 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Blue Fog, 1 p.
  - Boogie Woogie Lady
    5 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Brain Damage, 9 p. (Box 51)
    7 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Bright Moments, 3p. (Box 51)
  - Blue Essence, 3p. (Box 51)
  - Buckwheat's At The Session, 3p. (Box 51)
  - Buddy's Special, 1 p. (Box 40)
    Bassoon part only.
  - The Butterfly, 9p. (Box 51)
  - The Call, 17p. (Box 51)
    Lead sheet and 12 ensemble parts for various instruments.
    Photocopies also.
  - Can't Go Back, 6p. (Box 52)
  - Caravan, 32p. (Box 52)
    Orchestration by Horace Tapscott.
  - Children (Box 38)
    Score and lyrics, multiple copies.
  - Child In The World, 17p. (Box 52)
    Partial score and 11 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Child Of Love, 22p. (Box 52)
    Score and 8 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - City Called Heaven, 7p. (Box 52)
  - Clarisse (Box 38)
    Ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Close To Freedom, 27p. (Box 52)
    Score, 5 ensemble parts for various instruments, and lyric sheet.
  - A Close Encounter Of The Very Best Kind, 2 p. (Box 62)
  - Come Sunday, 4p. (Box 52)
    2 ensemble parts for piano and bass; vocal part. No lyrics.
  - The Coming Of The Dome, 30p. (Box 52)
    Two scores and 11 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Crepuscule With Nellie, 24p. (Box 52)
  - Crescent (Box 63)
    Incomplete ensemble parts for various instruments
  - Daddy Goodness (Stage play adapted from writings of Richard Wright) (Box 40)
    Listing of musical selections in order of appearance in Acts I and II. Sheet music for: Angel / Sanders & Franklin -- Spread Joy / Jimmy Radcliff -- Miracle
  - The Dark Tree, 40p. (Box 52)
    Score and 17 ensemble parts for various instruments.
    [Gordon Theil has lent the 2 page score to Alan Stevenson for a YRL exhibit, January-March 2006].
  - Daughter of Cochise (Box 38)
  - The Day the Sky Cried (Box 38)
    Score and notes.
  - Dem Folks (Box 52)
  - Dem Folks (Box 67)
  - Deon, 21p. (Box 52)
  - Departure, 22p. (Box 52)
  - Desert Fairy Princess (Box 40)
    Score and ensemble parts for various instruments
  - Dream Nigguh, 3p. (Box 52)
  - Echoes, 2 p. (Box 62)
    Lead sheet and lyric sheet.
  - Effie, 37p. (Box 52)
    Score dated 1966.
  - Efuru (Daughter Of The Heavens), 4 p. (Box 62)
  - Elaborations (Box 63)
    Alto part only.
  - Elysian Park, 16p. (Box 52)
  - Emanon, 22p. (Box 52)
    10 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Emerge, 2p. (Box 52)
    Tenor sax part.
  - The Entertainer, 1 p. (Box 62)
  - Evening's Last Sun Ray's (Box 38)
  - Evening's Last Sun Rays, 33p. (Box 53)
    16 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Exercises and Studies (Box 65)
    Contains various exercises for music study, including some music theory and course work.
  - Eye of The Storm, 30p. (Box 53)
  - Faith, 17p. (Box 53)
    Lead sheets included for That Ol' Bebop Rhythm by Roberto Miranda and Lino's Pad by Horace Tapscott.
  - Feels Good To Feel Good, 19p. (Box 53)
  - Flashback Of Time, 11p. (Box 53)
  - Flight 17, 39p. (Box 53)
    Score and 12 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Flight 17 (Box 53)
    Copies of score and various ensemble parts.
  - Flight 17(II Version), 3p. (Box 53)
  - For Fats, 17 p. (Box 53)
    Composer's name is also given as Black Arthur Blythe.
  - For Horace, 66p. (Box 53)
    Score dated August 20, 1967.
  - Free At Last, 5p. (Box 53)
    4 ensemble parts for various instruments.
  - Freedumb, 4p. (Box 53)
    Lead sheets.
  - Freedom's Sweet, 26p. (Box 53)
  - Future Sally's Time, 6p. (Box 53)
    Arthur Blythe is also called Black Arthur.
  - The Gathering (Box 54)
  - Gershwin Medley (Box 40)
    score
  - Giant Steps (Box 54)
  - The Giant Is Awakened (Box 54)
    Ensemble parts for various instruments
  - The Goat and Ram Jam (Box 54)
  - The Golden Pearl (Box 38)
    Score, ensemble parts for various instruments, and copies.
  - Good Bait, 1 p. (Box 63)
    Lead sheet
  - The Great Music Of Duke Ellington, 1973; 143 p. (Box 65)
    Sheet music for 42 compositions.
  - The Grip (Box 54)
  - Groovin' High (Box 63)
    Parts for piano and 1st Tenor Saxophone.
    Saxophone solo is written.
  - Half & Half (Box 54)
  - Haunted (Box 38)
    Several copies of English horn part.
  - Haunted (Box 54)
  - High Priest (Box 54)
    Score
  - Highway Flyers, 30p. (Box 62)
  - Horace (Box 38)
    Parts for piano, tenor, and bass. Music for "Shadows" (Tapscott) on the back of the piano part, "The Night Has A Thousand Eyes" on the back of the tenor part, "Aisha" on the back of the bass part.
  - Household of Saud (Box 54)
    Score and ensemble parts and for various instruments
  - I Have Sinned (Box 40)
    Parts for Trombone and Bass.
  - I Like The Sunrise (Box 40)
    Ensemble parts for various instrumnets.
  - I Remember Clifford (Box 40)
    Score and lead sheet
  - I Felt Spring (Box 54)
  - I Have Heard God's Call (Box 54)
  - I Wish You Love (Box 54)
  - If You Could See Me Now (Box 38)
    Score and ensemble parts.
  - Ifrane (Box 63)
    Score and bass part
  - I'm Goin To Tell God All My Troubles (Box 63)
    Sheet music for piano and voice
  - Impressions of the Ghetto (Box 54)